# FREDDY ROMO

## WEB DEVELOPER



#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Web Developer with more than 4 years working experience building and maintaining web sites using different technologies such as HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery and Wordpress. Spanish is my native language but quite fluent in English. I keep learning new technologies like React, TailwindCSS, Astro and more.

#### SKILLS

- Web Development: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, jQuery, WordPress, PHP
- Tools: Git, Astro, TailwindCSS

#### CONTACT

- +358449238102
- ★ Turenki, Finland
- https://github.com/FreddyRomoCH

#### **EDUCATION**

IES Pau Casesnoves, Mallorca, Spain 2009 - 2011

Advance Specific Vocational Training in Administration of Computer Systems

IES Pau Casesnoves, Mallorca, Spain 2007 - 2009

Vocational Training in Management of Computer Systems

#### LANGUAGES

• English: Fluent

• Spanish: Fluent

• Finnish: Beginner (actively learning)

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Agencia Raya - Santiago, Chile

Web Developer Apr 2015 - Aug 2018

- Gained experience building websites using HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery and PHP.
- Working with formularies and Databases (MySQL).
- Working with clients and designers to get best results with different points of view.

# Alianza - Santiago, Chile

Web Developer Apr 2014 - Apr 2015

- Building web sites using HTML, CSS, Javascript and Wordpress.
- Implementing responsive design for Email Marketing.
- Working side to side with clients to have a better user experience.

# Working Holiday, Australia & New Zealand

Various Roles Jan 2019 - Dec 2020

- I learned English, since it was my primary target during this adventure.
- I could gain experience in different fields like hospitality, agriculture and construction.
- I worked with people for different cultures and that gave me more communication skills and cultural awareness.